[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "How old your elder brother was 10 years before you was born, mate?",
    "variants": ["10 years", "11 years", "12 years", "14 years"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["10 years"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "2 + 2?",
    "variants": ["4", "2", "5", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["4", "4"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "3 + 3?",
    "variants": ["6", "2", "3", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["6"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "4 + 4?",
    "variants": ["8", "2", "3", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["8"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "5 + 5?",
    "variants": ["1", "10", "3", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["10"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "6 + 6?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "12", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["12"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "7 + 7?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "3", "14"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["14"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "8 + 8?",
    "variants": ["16", "2", "3", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["16"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "9 + 9?",
    "variants": ["1", "18", "3", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["18"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "10 + 10?",
    "variants": ["1", "20", "3", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["20"]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "11 + 11?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "22", "4"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["22"]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "12 + 12?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "3", "24"],
    "variantLetters": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    "trueAnswers": ["24"]
  }
]
